<resources>
    <string name="app_name">myConditions</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="pressure">PRESSURE</string>
    <string name="wind">WIND</string>
    <string name="humidity">HUMIDITY</string>
    <string name="clouds">CLOUDS</string>
    <string name="xc_conditions">XC Conditions</string>

    <!-- Type of day conditions   -->
    <string name="stickyDay">Expect strong hard edged thermals with bullet cores, strong sink and most likely blue sky.</string>
    <string name="fizzyDay">Expect softer thermals with cumulus cloud development. Should be pleasant to fly, head for base and follow the clouds!</string>
    <string name="soupDay">Not likely possible for big XC distance. Warm moist stable air is thick and soup like, thermals can’t move through it well.</string>
    <string name="windySticky">May be turbulent! Hard edged thermals with strong micro cores. Weak lifts gets blown away and expect descent turbulence.</string>
    <string name="windyFizzy">Windy unstable day. Possibility for cloud street formation.</string>
    <string name="morningGreet">Good morning! Later you will get your info. First thing is coffee!</string>

    <!-- SearchMode for the specific day -->
    <string name="stickyDay_search">Search wide and slow covering as much ground as possible with the best sink rate. Thermal will trigger on the most heated sources and fly over the mountain peaks.</string>
    <string name="fizzyDay_search">Thermals will trigger on slightest change in terrain. Usually best and strongest thermals are away from the mountain.</string>
    <string name="soupDay_search">Try to search for very good heated source on day like this and hope that there will be any lift.</string>
    <string name="windySticky_search">Search downwind of any good heated source on the ground. Towns and villages works good on a blue day.</string>
    <string name="windyFizzy_search">The best lift you will find on the upwind side of the cloud. If you are low, then search downwind from heated source on the ground.</string>
    <string name="morningGreet_search">Search for perfect spot to drink your coffee.</string>
    <string name="searchForBeer">Search for cold beer. Why not?</string>

    <!-- ClimbMode for the specific day -->
    <string name="stickyDay_climb">When you hit micro cores crank hard and tight as possible. You might get half turn in lift, but for sure you can climb like this. Fight for every meter and never give up!</string>
    <string name="fizzyDay_climb">Don\'t turn immediately, relax and feel the glider. Listen to your vario and work your 360 turns.</string>
    <string name="soupDay_climb">Try to listen your vario and hang for any climb rate you get.</string>
    <string name="windySticky_climb">Stronger cores punch trough and stay upwind. That is your goal, center your 360s on the upwind side of thermals.</string>
    <string name="windyFizzy_climb">Find the strongest lift by working the upwind side of the thermal.</string>
    <string name="morningGreet_climb">Good morning! Later you will get your info. First thing is coffee!</string>
    <string name="noThermalNoClimb">No thermals, no climbing.</string>
    <string name="stickyDay1">Expect strong hard edged thermals with bullet cores, strong sink and most likely blue sky.</string>


</resources>
